[Music]
in the RP sector there is a massive gap
of getting experienced Erp Consultants
especially when we look in the Dynamics
field and around business Central we
were also competing you know in the same
area we tried to search for uh the same
candidate so Partners which face uh
Talent Gap challenges now have the
option to join a program our reskilling
program and in this reskilling program
what we do is we recruit individuals
which come out of the industry and we
res skill them we retrain them to become
business Central professionals
Consultants or developers and we've
created the program in such a way that
it's really low risk and cost effective
for our business andal
partners the program exists out of three
pillars which the very first one is we
will hire people with industry
experience the second one is and we're
going to train the individuals both from
a product perspective and from a
professional skills perspective and then
lastly we're going to follow up on the
success of the individuals by coaching
them for a period of 6
months Microsoft Talent program offers
us you know a training program an
onboarding program to make sure that our
people are uh you know up and running as
soon as possible which is highly
important not only for us you know that
uh we can run our business but also for
our people that they have a perspective
in their career and enjoying what
they're
doing when I heard about the talent
program for the first time um the first
emotion was just pure excitement because
if Microsoft comes with a new initiative
you want to jump on the wagon and until
now it's been so successful and it's
been a great journey that we would like
to see what we can do in the future also
for other roles we have recently hired
two new uh employees from the
recruitment program it's been a great
process and uh we're very pleased with
the the new hires that we've brought on
board this is finally what we've been
looking for a way where Microsoft as the
publisher was partnering with us to try
to find that next Generation talent pool
that we really need to bring into the
ecosystem I was not at the moment how my
set of skills could mix well together
for a proper career path and then I
realized that being a Microsoft business
Central consultant could be the perfect
answer that I was looking for so what I
appreciate the most about the talent
program is that it combines both element
of practical work and the theoretical
aspects of the Erp system business
Central Dynamics it's really refreshing
to have such a guided program you don't
feel alone alone in it and you're with
the
community I knew I wanted to be some
sort of consultant and consultancy has
always been very interesting to me but I
didn't know that best Central was going
to be the one for me until I sort of
jumped into
it what I appreciate the most at trimit
is they are appreciating me as a person
and they trust my uh
ability clients first really allows me
to be creative in my Learning Journey
there's an in-depth interest in how I'm
going to learn best and how I'm going to
be best successful with the
organization I hope that I'm not only a
consultant 5 years from now but also 25
years from now so if you're still onou
on why you should join the reskilling
initiative let me give you five reasons
the very first one is we're going to be
able to find the right Candidate For You
Second from a prod and professional
skills learning perspective we're using
the best in the industry third
your new hires are going to be part of
something bigger a new hire Community
for your new hires were going to have a
lot of onboarding flexibility we can
onboard them any moment at any time and
then lastly it's low risk and very cost
effective so for partners who are
considering joining the Microsoft time
program I would really recommend that
it's a great way of growing new skill
sets within your business and that is
what is going to drive the future of
your business so get on board now fire
fire fire
fire